Finding Aid for the Fletcher Bascom Dresslar Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Publication Titles
  - General Principles..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Holograph Manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Good and Bad Air..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Greenfield, Ohio, High School..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated; 2 copies (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Grover Cleveland High School..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Grover Cleveland High School, St..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Growth and Culture..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Holograph Manuscript), undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Growth of the Dignity of Motherho..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Holograph Manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Happiness..., by Meyer, Adelphia (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Health Care of Rural School Chi..., by Wood, Thomas (Publication), undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Health Education in George Peab..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Holograph Manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Health Education in George Peab..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Health Teaching in Schools..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated; 3 copies (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Health Work in Schools..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), 1916 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Healthy Air..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated; 2 copies (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Heating and Ventilation..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - High School Commencement Ad..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated; Marked (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - History of Education in Europe..., by Cubberly, Ellwoo (Publication), 1899; Syllabus (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - How Can County Schools Be Ma..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated; Marked (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - How the Ellerbe Young Tar Heel..., by Meacham, Arthu (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - How to Live Longer and Be Happy..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), 1920 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - How to Prevent Worry..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Hutchinson, Kansas, High School..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Hygiene of Teaching Language,..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - In Memoriam..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), 1926; 2 (Box Mark, Folder 10)
  - Instructions Regarding Thesis W..., by Leland Stanford (Publication), 1901 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Invest in Yourselves ......., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Holograph Manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Investigations Made in Departme..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Janitor Service..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Jesus as a Teacher..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Holograph Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Left-Handedness..., by LeMar, Esther (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Lighting..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated; Marked (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Lighting of School Buildings..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated; 2 copies, one marked (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - List Board of Health Literature re..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Location of School Buildings..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Lowell High School..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - M.I.T. School Health Appraisal Fo..., by Turner, C.E. (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Manual Training..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Marshall's Pencils..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Holograph Manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Medical Inspection..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated; 2 copies (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Medical Inspection of Schools..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Memorial of Albert Homer Purdue..., by Ashley, George (Publication), 1918 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Money for Rural Schools..., by U.S. Department (Publication), undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Morning's Observation of a Baby,..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Publication), 1901 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - National Herbart Society..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated; Marked (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - New Central High School, Minnea..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated; 2 copies, one marked (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - New Education..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated; Marked (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - New High School Building, Green..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), 1914 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - New High School, South Bend, In..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated; 2 copies (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - New Method of Color Mixing, A..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Holograph Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - New Patriotism, A..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Holograph Manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - New Psychology and its Pedagogic..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Holograph Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Normality..., by Meyer, Adelphia (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - North Dakota State Board of Heal... (Publication), 1918 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Notes on Building Code for the St..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Of Youth..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated; Marked (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - On Boarding Schools..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Holograph Manuscript), 1907 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Open Air Schools..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated; 4 (Box Mark, Folder 10)
  - Organization and Supervision..., by Cubberly, Ellwoo (Publication), 1899; Syllabus (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Organization of the Interstate Sch..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Publication), 1930; Article in "School Life" (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Orientation..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated; Marked (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Orientation of Class Rooms..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated; 2 copies, one marked (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Outline of Report of Study of Sch..., by Dresslar, F.B. and (Typed Manuscript), undated; 4 (Box Mark, Folder 10)
  - Outline of the Hot Springs Summ..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Peabody Reflector and Alumni New... (Publication), 1920 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Physical Equipment for the Scho..., by Library Commiss (Publication), undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Playgrounds..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated; 2 copies, marked (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Portable Houses..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Possible Experiments..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Holograph Manuscript), undated; Notebook (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Prayer..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Holograph Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Press Release..., by North Carolina S (Publication), 1915 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Principals..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Projects in Sex Education..., by McCanless, Eva (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Psychology of Touch in General..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Holograph Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Relation of Character to Good He..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Holograph Manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Religion, Dogmantism in Science..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Holograph Manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Religious Forces in Higher Educa..., by Brown, Elmer Ell (Publication), 1900 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Report Survey Evanston, Illinois..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Report of Joint Committees on H..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Report of the Committee on Phys..., by Council of Educ (Publication), 1898 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Report of the Survey of the High..., by Brown, J. Stanle (Typed Manuscript), 1916 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Report on Standards for Element..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), 1928 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Reports of Department Committe..., by American Unitari (Publication), undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Requirements and Standards to be..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Rural School Hygiene..., by Rapeer, Louis W (Publication), 1914 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - School Architecture and Sanitation..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - School Building Decoration..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - School Buildings and Grounds..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - School Decoration..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - School Desks..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Holograph Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - School Sanitation..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - School as a Socializing Agency,..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated; Marked (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Sex Education..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Sierra Educational News and Book..., by Council of Educ (Publication), 1911 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Some Phases of Kindergarten Pr..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Holograph Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Some Problems to be Considere..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Some Suggestions Concerning D..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated; Marked (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - State Supervision of School Archi..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Study of Adolescence, The..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), 1891 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Suggestions from the Psychology..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Suggestions on Sketch Enclosed..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Suggestions on the Need for Sani..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Supervision of Teachers..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Survey, The..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Teacher, A Servant of the State,..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Teachers..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Holograph Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Tests and Measurements of Childre..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Holograph Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - The Future Location of City Scho..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Theory and Practice..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Holograph Manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - To What Extent are the School A..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Publication), undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - To define means to limit......., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Holograph Manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - To the Board of Education of, Th..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), 1910 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - To the Members of the National..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Toilets..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Toilets..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Trabajos de Higiene Escolar del..., by Unidentified (Publication), 1920 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Two Evils of Modern Immigration..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Holograph Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Tyranny of Tradition, The..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Unidentified..., by Unidentified (Holograph Manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Uniting the Home and School in He..., by Whitney, Anne (Publication), 1929 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Untitled..., by Franklin, W.S. (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Use of Score Cards in School Bui..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated; Marked (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Value of Child Study to the Currie..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated; Marked (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Ventilation..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Holograph Manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Ventilation and Heating of the Stock..., by Sundell, Carl (Typed Manuscript), 1907; Outline (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Vision..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Holograph Manuscript), undated; Notecard (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Voice in Spiritual Education, The..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated; Marked (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Volume on Superstition and Educati..., by Sierra Education (Publication), 1907 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - West Virginia University..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - What Parents Should Teach Thei..., by Weir, H.C. (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - What the Adolescent Girl Should..., by Jenkins, Mrs. (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - What the Appalachian Training S..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Holograph Manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Why I Plant a Garden..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Holograph Manuscript), undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Willys Knight..., by Willys-Overland, (Publication), 1927 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Windows..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Windows..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Womanhood and Its Development..., by Rummell, Luella (Publication), undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Work Space for Children in Elem..., by Dresslar, Fletcher (Typed Manuscript), undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Writings of Dr. Fletcher Bascom..., by Pruett, Haskell (Typed Manuscript), undated; 2 copies (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Outgoing Correspondence Index
  - Kalbach, L.A., Nov. 25, 1911 (Box 1)
  - Carmichael, O.C., Dec. 11, 1912 (Box 1)
  - Dearborn, George Van D., Dec. 11, 1912 (Box 1)
  - Hume, Edward H., Dec. 11, 1912 (Box 1)
  - Carrier Air Conditioning Co., Dec. 31, 1912 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., Dec. 31, 1912 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, L.D., Dec. 31, 1912 (Box 1)
  - Holland, E.O., Dec. 31, 1912 (Box 1)
  - McClain, E.L., Dec. 31, 1912 (Box 1)
  - MA Sanitary Appliance Co., Dec. 31, 1912 (Box 1)
  - Motyl, Joe, Dec. 31, 1912 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., 1912 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., 1912 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., Jan. 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Jan. 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Ormsby, Carrie 0., Jan. 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Brewster, Wales C., Jan. 3, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., Jan. 3, 1913 (Box 1)
  - DuShane, Daniel, Jan. 3, 1913 (Box 1)
  - King, Jennette M., Jan. 3, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McClain, E.L., Jan. 3, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Maphis, Charles G., Jan. 3, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Page, Thomas Walker, Jan. 3, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Johnson, R.C., Jan. 8, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kingsley, S.C., Jan. 8, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McClain, E.L., Jan. 8, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wehrhahn, Dr., Jan. 8, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Challman, S.A., Jan. 10, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Cheney, Charles Henry, Jan. 13, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., Jan. 13, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Jan. 13, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McClain, E.L., Jan. 13, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Norris, J.L., Jan. 13, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Jan. 14, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McClain, E.L., Jan. 14, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Storey, Thomas A., Jan. 13, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wood, Frank C., Jan. 14, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., Jan. 15, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Bureau of Education, Jan. 18, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Fisher, C.W., Jan. 18, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Henry, J. Earl, Jan. 18, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Jan. 18, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Ludlow and Peabody, Jan. 18, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McClain, E.L., Jan. 18, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Acme Asbestos Cover and Suppl, Jan. 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Brister, J.W., Jan. 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Bruere, R.W., Jan. 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Brewster, Wales C., Jan. 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Doll, E.A., Jan. 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Eggleston, J.D., Jan. 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goddard, H.H., Jan. 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., Jan. 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Hintrager, Carl, Jan. 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Voght, H.W., Jan. 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Whitcomb, J.E., Jan. 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wilson, Louis N., Jan. 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Woods, R.S., Jan. 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Gram, Franklin C., Jan. 23, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Little, R.I., Jan. 23, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McClain, E.L., Jan. 23, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., Jan. 24, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Payne, Bruce R., Jan. 24, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton. P.P., Jan. 25, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., Jan. 25, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Johnson, D.B., Jan. 25, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Rail, E.E., Jan. 25, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Yasinski, A.F., Jan. 25, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Acme Asbestos Cover and Suppl, Jan. 27, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., Jan. 27, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Dahlstrom Metalic Door Co., Jan. 27, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Palmer, T.W., Jan. 27, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Devendorf, B.A., Jan. 28, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Fisher, C.W., Jan. 28, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Judd, Zebulon, Jan. 28, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Morris, Agnes, Jan. 28, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Rail, E.E., Jan. 28, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Atlas School Supply Co., Jan. 29, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Brewster, Wales C., Jan. 29, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., Jan. 29, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Hood, W.R., Jan. 29, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Hood, W.R., Jan. 29, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Merritt and Co., Jan. 29, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Monroe, Paul, Jan. 29, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Rail, E.E., Jan. 29, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Yasinski, A.F., Jan. 29, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Foght, H.W., Jan. 31, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., Jan. 31, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Thesmar, Alix, Jan. 31, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Boykin, J.C., Feb. 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Brewster, Wales C., Feb. 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., Feb. 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Ittner, W.B., Feb. 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Feb. 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McClain, E.L., Feb. 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Canfield, George, Feb. 3, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McClain, E.L., Feb. 3, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McClain, E.L., Feb. 3, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Yasinski, A.F., Feb. 3, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Boykin, J.C., Feb. 5, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Cooper, Frank Irving, Feb. 5, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., Feb. 5, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Feb. 5, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Dry, M.B., Feb. 6, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Glaniel, M.M., Feb. 6, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Henry, J. Earl, Feb. 6, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McClain, E.L., Feb. 6, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Rail, E.E., Feb. 6, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., Feb. 7, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Dowling, Oscar, Feb. 7, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Ittner, W.B., Feb. 7, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Judd, Zebulon, Feb. 7, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Morris, Agnes, Feb. 7, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Byerly, H.E., Feb. 8, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McClain, E.L., Feb. 8, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Rail, E.E., Feb. 8, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., Feb. 10, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Rail, E.E., Feb. 10, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Yasinski, A.Y., Feb. 11, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Henry, J. Earl, Feb. 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., Feb. 13, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kennedy, D.C., Feb. 14, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McClain, E.L., Feb. 14, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Rail, E.E., Feb. 14, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wolcott, J.D., Feb. 14, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Doll, E.A., Feb. 15, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Ittner, William B., Feb. 15, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McClain, E.L., Feb. 15, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Brewster, W.C., Feb. 17, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., Feb. 17, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Doii,A.E., Feb. 17, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Blair, Francis G., Feb. 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Brewster, W.C., Feb. 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Hyatt, Edward, Feb. 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McCloskey, Alice G., Feb. 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Swearinger, J.E., Feb. 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Yasinski, A.F., Feb. 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kentucky State Board of Health, Feb. 22, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Doll, E.A., Feb. 27, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Fisher, C.W., Feb. 27, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Blair, Francis G., March 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., March 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., March 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Mark, E.H., March 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Swearingen, J.E., March 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - van Hoose, A.W., March 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Weinzirl, John, March 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Doster, James P., March 4, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kalbach, L.A., March 4, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McClain, E.L., March 4, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Mark, E.H., March 5, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Yasinski, A.Y., March 7, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Barnes, Earl, March 8, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Booker, Warren H., March 8, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., March 8, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Gregg, F.M., March 8, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Jones, S.B., March 8, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Roach, Walter W., March 8, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wood, Thomas D., March 8, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., March 10, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Corwin, R.W., March 10, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., March 10, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Ittner, William B., March 10, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McClain, E.L., March 10, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Cheney, Charles Henry, March 11, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., March 11, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Foster, James H., March 11, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Mark, E.H., March 11, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Payne, Bruce R., March 11, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Backus, Emma S., March 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Bruce, William G., March 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., March 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Phelps, Jessie, March 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wood, Thomas D., March 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Yasinski, A.Y., March 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Brewster, W.C., March 13, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Jones, S.B., March 13, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Ittner, William B., March 14, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McClain, E.L., March 14, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wood, Thomas D., March 14, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Ferguson, Calrow and Taylor, March 15, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Burton Range Company, March 17, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Frank A. Hall and Sons, March 17, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Maphis, Charles G., March 17, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Richmond Adjustable Window, March 17, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Ludlow and Peabody, March 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McClain, E.L., March 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Comins, H.M., March 22, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Green, Frederick R., March 22, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McCloskey, Alice G., March 22, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Maphis, Charles G., March 22, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Stevenson, T.J., March 22, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Taylor, R.E. Lee, March 22, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wood, Thomas D., March 22, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., March 24, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kalbach, L.A., March 24, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McCullough, J.E., March 24, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wood, Thomas D., March 24, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Fisher, C.W., March 25, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Postman, J.K., March 25, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Cheney, Charles J., March 27, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Green, Frederick R., March 27, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Keith, James, March 27, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Speed, James, March 27, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Yasinski, A.F., March 27, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Ittner, William B., March 28, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McClain, E.L., March 28, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wood, Thomas D., March 28, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Doelle, Jonathan A., March 29, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Rail, R.E., March 29, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wolcott, Jonathan D., March 29, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McClain, E.L., Oct. 8, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Narramore, F.A., Oct. 8, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Brown, Henry E., Oct. 30, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Carter, H.E., Oct. 30, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Challman, S.A., Oct. 30, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Crosier, M.E., Oct. 30, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Downes, F.E., Oct. 30, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., Oct. 30, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., Oct. 30, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Rasor, Alpha, Oct. 30, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Thackston, John A., Oct. 30, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Doster, James J., Nov. 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Nov. 1, 1913 (Box 1)